// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " He didn't work hard …………………… he failed his exam.",
    answer: "so",
    options: [ "so", "because","as","therefore" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "………………… had the hunter raised the gun, than the birds flew away.",
    answer: "No sooner",
    options: ["As soon as","No sooner","Hardly","As long as"]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"She is …………………… intelligent to be defeated.",
    answer: "too",
    options: [
      "too", "so","very","none of these" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "…………………… had she got the message when she started.",
    answer: "Scarcely",
    options: ["Hardly","Scarcely","No sooner","As soon as" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "……………………… my children are employed, I have no financial difficulties.",
    answer: "Now that",
    options: [ "Now that", "Now","That","Because" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "They still live in the house ………………………… was built by their grandfather.",
    answer: "which",
    options: ["which", "how","who","what"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "……………………… he saw a dog, he threw stones at it.",
    answer: "Whenever",
    options: [ "When", "Whenever","Unless","However" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "You should neither see him …………………… call him.",
    answer: "nor",
    options: [ "or", "nor","and","not" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "…………………… he is honest, everybody respects him.",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [ "Since", "As","Because","All of the above" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "……………………. my mother is a doctor, she knows how to dress a wound.",
    answer: "As",
    options: [  "As", "So","If","All of above"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "You will not be able to meet him ……………………… you arrive in time.",
    answer: "unless",
    options: [  "unless", "if","without","until" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: " …………………… his health is poor, he attends his office regularly.",
    answer: "Although",
    options: [  "Although", "However","As","Because" ]
  },
];